Guide to the Communications Workers of America Records WAG.124
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VIII: Departments/Divisions/Districts, 1937-1991
  - Subseries VIII:C: CWA Departments, 1937-1991
    - Subsubseries VIII:C:5: Legal Department, 1957-1991
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (450-66-6956), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 14)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (483-56-2031), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 15)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (486-40-2310), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 16)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (486-50-2357), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 17)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (487-52-3492), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 18)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (488-46-8937), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 19)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (488-50-7533), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 20)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (488-52-5092), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 21)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (488-58-1841), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 22)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (488-62-6748), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 23)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (489-44-4701), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 24)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (489-54-1014), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 25)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (490-42-3964), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 26)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (490-48-2341), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 27)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (490-60-7970), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 28)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (491-48-3496), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 29)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (491-52-4984), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 200, Folder 30)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (491-52-6858), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 1)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (492-50-2681), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 2)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (493-48-6450), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 3)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (493-56-7524), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 4)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (493-58-3442), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 5)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (494-46-0351), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 6)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (495-42-8732), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 7)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (495-52-7421), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 8)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (497-48-1911), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 9)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (495-60-1020), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 10)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (496-46-9766), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 11)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (496-46-9839), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 12)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (497-38-8701), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 13)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (497-44-7867), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 14)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (497-44-8313), Jul 10, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 15)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (497-46-1787), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 16)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (498-42-7815), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 17)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (499-44-2070), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 18)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (498-54-0719), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 19)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (499-46-1394), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 20)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (499-46-1879), Jul 10, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 21)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (499-46-3368), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 22)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (499-52-5128), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 23)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (500-44-3318), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 24)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (500-50-3057), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 25)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (511-40-0430), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 26)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Kansas City Works (515-38-9509), Jul 5, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 27)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Practice Info./A Discovery Process, 1965-1990 (Box 201, Folder 28)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Practice Info./A Discovery Process, 1990 (Box 201, Folder 29)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Practice/Layoff Information, 1990 (Box 202, Folder 1)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Correspondence, 1989 (Box 202, Folder 2)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Various Pleadings, 1989-1990 (Box 202, Folder 3)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Correspondence, Jun 11, 1990-Oct 31, 1990, 1990 (Box 202, Folder 4)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Correspondence, Nov 1, 1990-Nov 21, 1990 (Box 202, Folder 5)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Correspondence (Computational Analysis EEOC vs. AT&T) Nov 23, 1990-Jan 2, 1991 (Box 202, Folder 6)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Notes and Research, 1990-1991 (Box 202, Folder 7)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: List of Claimants (1 of 9), pages 1-297, May 29, 1990 (Box 202, Folder 8)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: List of Claimants (2 of 9), pages 301-599, May 29, 1990 (Box 202, Folder 9)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: List of Claimants (3 of 9), pages 600-899, May 29, 1990 (Box 202, Folder 10)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: List of Claimants (4 of 9), pages 900-1199, May 29, 1990 (Box 202, Folder 11)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: List of Claimants (5 of 9), pages 1200-1499, May 29, 1990 (Box 203, Folder 1)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: List of Claimants (6 of 9), pages 1500-1799, May 29, 1990 (Box 203, Folder 2)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: List of Claimants (7 of 9), pages 1800-2099, May 29, 1990 (Box 203, Folder 3)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: List of Claimants (8 of 9), pages 2100-2399, May 29, 1990 (Box 203, Folder 4)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: List of Claimants (9 of 9), pages 2400-2678, May 29, 1990 (Box 203, Folder 5)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Bargaining: Western Electric Materials, 1968, 1983 (Box 203, Folder 6)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Correspondence, Jan 1991 (Box 203, Folder 7)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Correspondence, Feb 1991 (Box 203, Folder 8)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Correspondence, Mar 1991-Apr 1991 (Box 203, Folder 9)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Correspondence, May 1991-Jun 1991 (Box 203, Folder 10)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Legal Briefs, Exhibits, First Interrogatories of Defendant, 1973 (Box 204, Folder 1)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Legal Briefs, Response to Interrogatories, Correspondence, 1974-1975, undated (Box 204, Folder 2)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Pre-Litigation Delay Issue, 1974, 1990 (Box 204, Folder 3)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Correspondence, 1979, 1991 (Box 204, Folder 4)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Correspondence, 1991 (Box 204, Folder 5)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Columbus Works Arbitration, 1986, 1988 (Box 204, Folder 6)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Correspondence (Settlement Proposal, Cases), 1986, 1991 (Box 204, Folder 7)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Consent Decree (Sherry Eirhart v. Libbey-Owens-Ford Co. And LOF Glass Inc., 1987 (Box 204, Folder 8)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Maternity Leave Newsletter, 1990 (Box 204, Folder 9)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Stipulation of Settlement, Feb 25, 1991 (Box 204, Folder 10)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Settlement Agreement Draft, Apr 24, 1991 (Box 204, Folder 11)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Correspondence, Mar 1991-Apr 1991 (Box 204, Folder 12)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: EEO Update Program Paper, Cases, Apr 4, 1991 (Box 204, Folder 13)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Settlement Agreement Issues/Cases, 1991 (Box 204, Folder 14)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Wage Trends/Statistics, 1970-1975 (Box 204, Folder 15)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Layoffs; Recall Rights, 1971-1978, 1990-1991, undated (Box 204, Folder 16)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Cases from John Morgan's Files, 1972, 1976 (Box 205, Folder 1)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Surface Wiremen - Job Grades, 1973, undated (Box 205, Folder 2)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Surplus and Layoff, Apr 16, 1975 (Box 205, Folder 3)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Surplus, 1975 (Box 205, Folder 4)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Correspondence, 1977 (Box 205, Folder 5)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Final Bargaining Reports, 1977, undated (Box 205, Folder 6)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Bargaining Materials, 1986 (Box 205, Folder 7)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Budget Projections, 1989-1990 (Box 205, Folder 8)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Correspondence, 1990 (Box 205, Folder 9)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Settlement Proposals, 1990 (Box 205, Folder 10)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Conversations with CWA Officials Regarding Bargaining & Damage Issues, 1990 (Box 205, Folder 11)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Print-outs, Analysis and Data (Kansas City Works), 1990, undated (Box 205, Folder 12)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Killingsworth Computations and Analysis, 1990, undated (Box 205, Folder 13)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Settlement Agreement Drafts, 1990Apr 1991, 1991 (Box 205, Folder 14)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Settlement Agreement Drafts, May 1991 (Box 205, Folder 15)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Proposed Legislation, May 10, 1991 (Box 205, Folder 16)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Releases, IBEW Proposal, Mar 1991-Jun 1991 (Box 205, Folder 17)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: IBEW Contracts, 1991, undated (Box 205, Folder 18)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Summary of One Employee's Local File from Kansas City, 1966-1987 (Box 205, Folder 19)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Summary of One Employee's Local File from Kansas City, 1968-1988 (Box 205, Folder 20)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Correspondence/Settlement Proposal/Maternity Statistics, 1974, 1987-1990 (Box 205, Folder 21)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Correspondence/Notes, 1975, 1990, undated (Box 205, Folder 22)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Wage Incentive Plan, 1980, 1990 (Box 205, Folder 23)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Bridging/Memos/Notes, 1982, 19871990 (Box 205, Folder 24)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Exclusions (Non-Weco Facilities), 1986, 1990, undated (Box 205, Folder 25)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Reinstatement Analysis, 1987, 1990 (Box 205, Folder 26)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Damages/Mitigation Research/Cases, 1988-1990 (Box 206, Folder 1)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Correspondence, Wage Rates, Cases, 1988, 1990, undated (Box 206, Folder 2)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Statement of General Information on Maternity Leave Practices, Apr 16, 1990 (Box 206, Folder 3)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Sample Questionnaire for Claimants, Apr 23, 1990 (Box 206, Folder 4)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Calculation of Back Pay, Jun 18, 1990 (Box 206, Folder 5)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Memos (Paralegal Projects for September, Date Entry), Aug 29, 1990-Sep 3, 1990, undated (Box 206, Folder 6)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Settlement Proposal Outline, Sep 1990 (Box 206, Folder 7)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: CWA/IBEW Officials, Sep 1990 (Box 206, Folder 8)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Memos/Notes (Conferences with Attorneys), 1990 (Box 206, Folder 9)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Correspondence - Sept. 12 Conference, 1990 (Box 206, Folder 10)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Sample of Women Who Filed Claims, 1990 (Box 206, Folder 11)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Requests to CWA Local's Responses, 1990 (Box 206, Folder 12)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Settlement Reports (Exclusions), 1990 (Box 206, Folder 13)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Settlement (Statistics, Pension Plan Survey), 1990 (Box 206, Folder 14)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Settlement (Meetings with Defendant's Counsel et al.), 1990 (Box 206, Folder 15)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Damage Estimates/U.S. District Court Judge Decision, 1990 (Box 206, Folder 16)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Special Pension Option Plan/SIPP, 1990 (Box 206, Folder 17)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Lauren Heberle's Work Files/Employee Benefit Brochures, 1977-1984, 1988, 1991 (Box 206, Folder 18)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: A Primer for Bell System Collective Bargaining in 1983, Jan 25, 1983 (Box 206, Folder 19)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Correspondence (Late Supplements by Claimants), 1990-1991 (Box 206, Folder 20)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Fringes, 1990, undated (Box 206, Folder 21)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Southwestern ABC Agenda Minutes, 1967, 1968, 1970 (Box 206, Folder 22)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Southwestern ABC Minutes, 1971 (Box 206, Folder 23)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Southwestern ABC Minutes, 1972 (Box 207, Folder 1)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Southwestern ABC Minutes, 1973 (Box 207, Folder 2)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Southwestern ABC Minutes, 1974 (Box 207, Folder 3)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Southwestern ABC Minutes, 1975 (Box 207, Folder 4)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Southwestern ABC Minutes, 1976 (Box 207, Folder 5)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Southwestern ABC Minutes, 1977 (Box 207, Folder 6)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Southwestern ABC Minutes, 1978-1980 (Box 207, Folder 7)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Interim Fees, 1989-1990 (Box 207, Folder 8)
      - EEOC vs. AT&T Technologies Inc.: Billing and Costs, 1990-1991 (Box 207, Folder 9)
      - Benedict vs. SW Bell & Local 12132: Separation Proposal/ Grievance Materials, 1980 (Box 208, Folder 1)
      - Benedict vs. SW Bell & Local 12132: Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 208, Folder 2)
      - Benedict vs. SW Bell & Local 12132: Pleadings (Gray Aff. Exhibit B), 1982, 1984 (Box 208, Folder 3)
      - Benedict vs. SW Bell & Local 12132: Pleadings (File III, A), 1983 (Box 208, Folder 4)
      - Benedict vs. SW Bell & Local 12132: Discovery, 1983 (Box 208, Folder 5)
      - Benedict vs. SW Bell & Local 12132: Deposition of Wayne H. Benedict, Feb 8, 1983 (Box 208, Folder 6)
      - Benedict vs. SW Bell & Local 12132: Deposition of Howard Pyle, Jan 1984 (Box 208, Folder 7)
      - Benedict vs. SW Bell & Local 12132: Notes, undated (Box 208, Folder 8)
      - Benedict vs. SW Bell & Local 12132: Cases, undated (Box 208, Folder 9)
      - CWA (AFL-CIO) vs. General Telephone Co. of California, 1981, undated (Box 208, Folder 10)
      - CWA, ITT Mackay Marine ADV., Silvers, Christopher Silvers, 1979 (Box 208, Folder 11)
      - CWA Psych. Tech. Union, Local 11555 vs. David Loberg and Al M. Loeb, 1982-1983 (Box 208, Folder 12)
      - CWA vs. Southwestern Bell Tel. Co., 1980-1981 (Box 208, Folder 13)
      - CWA vs. Southwestern Bell Tel. Co., 1982-1983 (Box 208, Folder 14)
      - John Harper et al. Vs. South Central Bell Telephone. Co., 1983-1985 (Box 208, Folder 15)
      - Joel Evan Laney vs. South Central Bell Telephone, Inc., 1982 (Box 208, Folder 16)
      - Mark Gary Lockweed vs. CWA, AFL-CIO Local 11575, 1980 (Box 208, Folder 17)
      - Georgia F. Lyles vs. CWA Local 11513 and Pacific Tel. &Teleg. Co., 1983-1984 (Box 208, Folder 18)
      - McRae, Hice, Speegle vs. South Central Bell Tel. Co.& CWA, 1983 (Box 208, Folder 19)
      - Michael L. Tyan vs. South Central Bell Tel. Co. & CWA, 1982-1983 (Box 208, Folder 20)
      - Sheridan vs. Gen. Tel. Co.: Correspondence; Disciplinary Action Reports, 1978-1982 (Box 208, Folder 21)
      - Sheridan vs. Gen. Tel. Co.: Discovery, 1979-1981, 1983 (Box 208, Folder 22)
      - Sheridan vs. Gen. Tel. Co.: Notes, 1980, 1982-1983, undated (Box 208, Folder 23)
      - Sheridan vs. Gen. Tel. Co.: Orders, 1982 (Box 208, Folder 24)
      - Sheridan vs. Gen. Tel. Co.: Discovery, 1982-1983 (Box 208, Folder 25)
      - Sheridan vs. Gen. Tel. Co.: Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 208, Folder 26)
      - Sheridan vs. Gen. Tel. Co.: Pleadings, 1982-1983 (Box 208, Folder 27)
      - Sheridan vs. Gen. Tel. Co.: Status Reports, 1983 (Box 208, Folder 28)
      - Robert A. Bache, Jr.: Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 209, Folder 1)
      - Robert A. Bache, Jr.: Correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 209, Folder 2)
      - Lorenzo Camps vs. Chesapeake and Potomac Tel. Co., 1981-1982 (Box 209, Folder 3)
      - Coca vs. Juan Ortiz, Ann Buchler, 1981 (Box 209, Folder 4)
      - CWA vs. AT&T: Correspondence, 1980 (Box 209, Folder 5)
      - CWA vs. N.Y. Tel. Co.: Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 209, Folder 6)
      - CWA vs. N.Y. Tel. Co.: Discovery, 1977-1978 (Box 209, Folder 7)
      - CWA vs. N.Y. Tel. Co.: Notes, undated (Box 209, Folder 8)
      - Dickerson vs. Bell Tel. Lab: Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 209, Folder 9)
      - Dickerson vs. Bell Tel. Lab: Complaint, Judgement, Proposed Findings, 1979, 1981 (Box 209, Folder 10)
      - Gamal Elmarsafi vs. Empire City Subway Co., Ltd, and CWA Dist.1, 1980-1981 (Box 209, Folder 11)
      - Green, Robert Louis vs. Community School Board No. 9, 1980 (Box 209, Folder 12)
      - Hayden vs. N.J. Bell, IBEW 827 and CWA, 1981-1982 (Box 209, Folder 13)
      - Hayden vs. N.J. Bell, IBEW 827 and CWA, 1981-1982 (Box 209, Folder 14)
      - Alexander James vs. Juan U. Ortiz: Corr., 1981 (Box 209, Folder 15)
      - Alexander James vs. Juan U. Ortiz: Pleadings, 1981-1982 (Box 209, Folder 16)
      - Arno Lind vs. Local 1020, CWA: Discovery, 1979 (Box 209, Folder 17)
      - Arno Lind vs. Local 1020, CWA: Pleadings, 1981-1982 (Box 209, Folder 18)
      - Arno Lind vs. Local 1020, CWA: Correspondence, 1979, 1981 (Box 209, Folder 19)
      - National Association of Social Workers, Inc. vs. CWA and Fed Mediation Conciliation Svc.: Complaint, Settlement Agreement, 1988 (Box 209, Folder 20)
      - National Association of Social Workers, Inc. vs. CWA and Fed. Mediation, 1988 (Box 209, Folder 21)
      - NBC et al. Vs. CWA: Restraining Orders/Corr., 1987-1988 (Box 209, Folder 22)
      - NBC et al. Vs. CWA: Pleadings, 1987-1988, undated (Box 209, Folder 23)
      - State of N.J. vs. Local 195, IFPTE and Local 518, SEIU - Pleadings, 1981-1982 (Box 209, Folder 24)
      - State of N.J. vs. Local 195, IFPTE and Local 518, SEIU - Pleadings, 1981-1982 (Box 209, Folder 25)
      - Visiting Nurse Assoc. of Buffalo, N.Y., Inc. vs. CWA: Order to Show Cause, Petition for Removal, 1980-1981 (Box 209, Folder 26)
      - Anderson v. Southern Bell, CWA and CWA 3224: Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 210, Folder 1)
      - Richard Baylis vs. N.Y. Tel. Co., CWA and Local 1104, 1983-1984 (Box 210, Folder 2)
      - Felix Dean Boatner vs. CWA: Correspondence, 1981 (Box 210, Folder 3)
      - Marian G. Castenedo vs. Southwestern Bell Tel. Co: Correspondence, 1974 (Box 210, Folder 4)
      - Marian G. Castenedo vs. Southwestern Bell Tel, Co.: Response in Opposition to Plaintiffs' Motion for Class Certification, Aug 1980 (Box 210, Folder 5)
      - The Chesapeake and Potomac Tel. Co. vs. CWA Exhibits A, B &C, 1981 (Box 210, Folder 6)
      - The Chesapeake and Potomac Tel. Co. vs. CWA: Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 210, Folder 7)
      - The Chesapeake and Potomac Tel. Co. vs. CWA: Notes, undated (Box 210, Folder 8)
      - The Chesapeake and Potomac Tel. Co. vs. CWA: Grievance File, 1982-1983 (Box 210, Folder 9)
      - The Chesapeake and Potomac Tel. Co. vs. CWA: Pleadings(summons & counterclaim), 1981-1982 (Box 210, Folder 10)
      - The Chesapeake and Potomac Tel. Co. vs. CWA: Pleadings (attachments 1-9), 1983, undated (Box 210, Folder 11)
      - CWA vs. The Chesapeake and Potomac Tel. Co.:Correspondence, 1978-1983, undated (Box 210, Folder 12)
      - CWA vs. N.J. Civil Service Comm.: Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 210, Folder 13)
      - CWA Local 1033 vs. State of N.J. CWA Case No. 1-82-546, 1983 (Box 210, Folder 14)
      - Daisy E. DeWindt vs. Joseph T. McGough, Jr.: Notice of Petition/ Stipulation Settling the Case, 1982-1983 (Box 210, Folder 15)
      - Elvira vs. Gandara vs. CWA Local 6228: Order of Dismissal, May 1981-Jun 1981 (Box 210, Folder 16)
      - Jose Gareia vs. Juan U. Ortiz: Correspondence, 1981, 1983 (Box 210, Folder 17)
      - Robert Hudson vs Southwestern Bell, Local 6222: Correspondence, 1974-1976 (Box 210, Folder 18)
      - Gwenivear James vs. CWA Local 3204 & Southern Bell Tel. Co.: Pleadings1981-1983 (Box 210, Folder 19)
      - Michael & Debra Johns vs. CWA Local 9118: Correspondence/Pleadings 1983-1984 (Box 210, Folder 20)
      - Ohio Public Workers vs. CWA/Council of Public Worker:Corr.; Complaint1983-1984 (Box 210, Folder 21)
      - Philip R. Michael and the N.Y.C. Dept. of Finance vs. Arthur Cheliotes: 1982-1983 Summons/Petition (Box 210, Folder 22)
      - James W. Raleigh v. Western Electric Co., Inc. and CWA Local 3060: Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 210, Folder 23)
      - Vincent Rovinette and Arthur Morgan vs. N.Y. Tel. Co., CWA Local 1108: Correspondence/Motions, 1983-1984 (Box 210, Folder 24)
      - Debra Samuel (Damon Samuel) vs. Oakland City, CWA: Correspondence, 1981-1983 (Box 210, Folder 25)
      - Debra Samuel ( Damon Samuel) vs. Oakland City and CWA: Pleadings, 1982, undated (Box 210, Folder 26)
      - Joseph Sandberg vs. James Kraushopf: Corr./ Notice of Petition, 1981-1983 (Box 210, Folder 27)
      - Martha Stallings vs. Southwestern Bell Tel. Co., CWA Local 12222 and CWA: Correspondence, 1976-1980 (Box 210, Folder 28)
      - James M. Thomsen et al. Vs. Western Electric Co., Inc.: Correspondence, 1981 (Box 210, Folder 29)
      - Lilly Vela and Lucretia Jackson vs. Western Electric, Dallas Works and CWA Local 12260: Correspondence/Summons, 1980 (Box 210, Folder 30)
      - Williams vs. Southern Bell and CWA: Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 210, Folder 31)
      - Suzanne Barr vs. Cincinnati Bell and CWA: Correspondence, 1976, 1980 (Box 211, Folder 1)
      - Cathy Blair vs. Southwestern Bell Inc.: Discovery, 1982-1983 (Box 211, Folder 2)
      - William Brink and CWA vs. Rex E. McQueen: Corr./Notes/ Pleadings, 1981 (Box 211, Folder 3)
      - Margaret Cooh vs. Southwestern Bell Co.: Corr., 1983 (Box 211, Folder 4)
      - CWA Local 5818 vs. Indiana Bell Tel. Co.: Motions/Memorandums, 1980, undated (Box 211, Folder 5)